a blackboard and a pen.
this even shy one sells.
come with me.
rascal.
play it.
Five for nothing.
one vote.
a paçoca.
neymar deserves to go to the cup.
yes or no?
Yes. here.
all four.
it's five.
will take four.
paçoquinha. then.
oh there.
the bro is already here.
already.
he was with six.
father,
ten. vote.
hand.
it took a while.
vote with paçoca
Yes it is.
here.
Oh.
I already change the score here.
hi brother.
thanks.
how much
did you send it?
nine reais.
bro.
who else goes to the cup?
Yes. obvious.
I'm crazy brother.
Valeuzão.
Worth. ten.
It's with family.
there is a child there.
ready.
take a picture.
it's us.
too much dough.
bro.
also takes the partner who is there.
Valeu. bro.
we are together. there.
here. o hand.
to play yet.
how many are there? four.
two. sleeve.
bro,
oh there. O. our.
There's a lot.
bro.
that this
it's selling paçoca too.
father,
will you say yes or no
here.
the kit.
here. O.
I'm here selling paçoquinha.
he bought it and he's strengthening me here.
bro.
too much.
brother.
tamo together.
hand,
how much is it to enter the stadium?
bro,
more or less as you wish.
It's only one hundred and fifty.
one hundred and fifty reais.
I'll watch the game here at the bar.
bro.
because too expensive
it's galerinha.
looks like it worked well.
brother.
i have thirty days to set up a business
and if you want to know what it's going to turn out to be.
already follows.
there.
it took.
tamo together.